Faculty Women's Club. Administrative files. 1919-2000.
UCLA Library Special Collections
Faculty Women's Club. Administrative files.
1919-2000
University Archives Record Series 83
UCLA Library Special Collections
0.4 linear ft. (1 box)
Record Series 83 contains the administrative files of the Faculty Women's Club at UCLA. Files regard the Southland Campus Women's Clubs Conference, Faculty Center, and other administrative activities.
Faculty Women's Club.
Access
COLLECTION STORED OFF-SITE AT SRLF: Open for research. Advance notice required for access. Contact the UCLA Library Special Collections Reference Desk for paging information.
Scope and Content
Record Series 83 contains the administrative files of the Faculty Women's Club at UCLA. Files regard the Southland Campus Women's Clubs Conference, Faculty Center, and other administrative activities.
This is an active record series; additional University records are expected to be added.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 3521012
- FWC Relations with the Faculty Center., 1919-1973. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Faculty Center - balance sheets., 1964-1972. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Faculty Center - minutes of meetings., 1964-1973. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Faculty Center - constitution, by laws., 1954-1969. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Victory Chest, U.S. War Bonds., 1945-1946. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- G. I. "Gift list.", 1952. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- International Student Center., 1962-1964. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Southland Colleges with Faculty Women's Clubs., 1963-1971. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Sunset Canyon Recreation Center., 1965-1969. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Tax exempt status., 1973-1974. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Silver inventory., 1973-1975. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Southland Campus Women's Clubs Conference., 1993-1994. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Southland Campus Women's Clubs Conference., 1995-1996. (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Southland Campus Women's Clubs Conference., 1998-1999. (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Southland Campus Women's Clubs Conference., 1999-2000. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Silverplate spoons, History Project., 1999. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Computer screens., 1999-2000. (Box 1, Folder 17)